In the
a. Group the in
the
a. Group. Who
were rooting through
a. Long
. Long.
Day of it your desk I
never go through again darling. I
wasn't expecting the pleasure of
a visit how I'm not used to being locked
out of your own home I know your house
your room your bedroom I just
sleep my apology you're in
a house I pity you after I get my
divorce. When I asked Will that be
me off laugh I am after
you then an old love letters.
That too smart to write it any Thanks for
not stopping my bank account the fact I
buy a plane ticket to Seattle
last the car you can do for
a friend much more latitude though is
a by the way why did you pick
him up. Three years of misery
and I mean don't and don't forget to change
your will you take yourself on to the
pink cloud if you accidentally
left anything to me.
Were.
The kind of column common type of engine
of
a side effect of column No not all the kind
of columns but you right now this is the
brother was calling.
For the chief say. Gone
I'm sad maybe you should know
sold him on taking me off
Market Street I've got you
as of now at your desk is.
Govern week on I'm starting to. On the
cheap hopes I can teach you something I
doubt it so I at least will be figuring
a case from two different angles. Here.
For me over that
one of mine. Want to want to be
a baby sure Mark mom will put
a both on the battle Thanks
a lot of Market Street mileage on
this I'm going to rest my dog for
a year. Press them on your I mean you got
on the leg work when you got back or gal
Koch
a minute ago. And he hung up right she
said. Be the one what it right for
the one that's been under your skin the
past few months I know it's none of my
business you've always played your women
pretty close to the vest but why don't you
find a girl it's good for
you like Janet is from
a settled. Or from me that's.
As we're as good
a race there's no good with us the way it
is right you don't have to down here name
their way to write.
A love song and I've been trying to
reach you you know enough for only you
got to see you come right over how to find
I am going to hold my own no no no we
got to be after he finds the he bought
a gun he finally feel me I know
if he can be any other we wait
a minute you don't like since he's going
to Seattle really gonna kill you he's not
a had to make it with guns before I can't
find it but now with an infection from
the floor in his room he musta been
a rap and he at the door
locked me you did OK I'll be
over soon for.
Your number OK Hi Janet.
What have you got
a week starting to the one hundred on the
night that you'll find see it and stop
fucking everything kind of thing
but on the salary now we can have
a part of what we're going to do with my
before bed I'm down in your studio in the
club come on television time and
a guy got some business on the
brain that I am going to follow
up. The other writing down because again
it's something that the living room you
can put flowers. They had on
cars or working down pat. I'm
like wow you're married into
a mighty fine family was the last
better thing happened to you I'll have
a bet. If
you took one look at this house I'm alone
I've been too frightened to appear here
or right down the come on I'll show it
to you before for me to not not all I
think of it so that about
a possible your father will know you
see me because he put it back in
a different place and I'm thinking
what am I going to do first for
years over drink and calm down to
the nice calm feeling I get from
a particular kind of a parent my son
a month I believe that he loved me for
life and he was in love all right my
mind he wished he had gone love that
so much already demoted to keep it and
get married I did the
and I'm glad there. Are
a big girl out of the plane
and you don't you and.
I were over there and I'm going to make
the drink when we ran the on the table.
You would. Know
how they did and they I've found
always you're just going to carry on.
You.
Know what to do to me. Get into
the strokes in the chest
you know what I'm doing
all the balcony door open
for the do I have anyone else to grow the
way you know that you
know what was going to be
think of you the truth can
get you're twenty years.
You could rest up or the
Get me the munis for
United Airlines. I'm
trying OK Mr Howard Craig trying to
not see out of the picture right
now oh it's still there are terms he
leaves eleven fifty and I thank him
Boyle Oh thank you very for
Priester the chair you have
had if you were going to come out if I
can get him back to the airport and
set up an alibi for himself is going to
work for you to check his bag for office
from the garage for the parking ticket
which only did years ago but he got killed
in Iraq where he didn't stay in
a bar or wandering
around. The enough nerve
of the cover.
It might have been called.
Back inside a cassette that
whatever happens you don't know
a lot of it. Hey wait
a minute and the parts Mark don't let anyone
not really up on the ball and covered
it up.
Making out I made you know that we can
reach the main airport building this way.
But your please tell me if we
got the main thrust right.
Really that damage before I ask him
a civil question would be
mightily to build me didn't know.
Any time anyone I would not go back on
a ferry ride from out of my dock my brother
right here they can't going to get
married I'm going to be best man.
What are you doing looking for
a green coat some guy got knocked
off after a lucky you're driving
a blue and I get disappointed by. That I
mean what you're coming across on the.
Phoenix y'all and I'm packing. Long.
Long way.
For Fraser thirty four and married to
a three seven zero zero down Mar
driver's license number thirty eight one
nine seven six OK that's it Bill how have
these checks at the lab for prints done
me for copy of the report when
you hear Hello Doc Doc just
a couple more questions one about time of
death not less than two hours ago or more
before the plane might make it more exact
but that's the best I can do right now OK
thanks to those blood stains on the shirt.
You know just the way they went and two
different directions go well maybe
he wasn't killed around here at all
Barbara Barbara had been pressuring Romber
Beauregard to support him and going on
all just checking back to your brother
thanks for the government no more questions
no no not for your dad OK you are nothing
and nothing when
a tad of this waiting on me and we have
every desire of course to exist in the
workings of justice if we do wish they'd
let the world lady will try and hurry them
now Mr Quimby can you help us fix the time
a little more exactly I mean when you saw
the other car discover the body where in
the city I should say it was in the
neighborhood those ten o'clock what do you
think you get the M.
And the maverick back with the back can you
just update you know why we love Barry
did not need to get out one hundred
ten o'clock and what do we see
a friend on an old friend of the family
so I think the thing now can you add
anything to your description of this other
car green Koobface that it was medium
size not new and fortunately I was on the
fact that I'd let him die and naturally
all I saw was a doctor say to him I
prayed I can help much more it was just
a car green of course and a
good pay I had a green coupe
a back in one nine hundred thirty one
individual nine hundred thirty three D.
At fifty back with the E.F.
Yes thank you now was there anyone
in it Mr Quimby besides the driver
let me think now. When I leaned
out and asked my civil question
I don't know I'm sure there was only the
right man wanted to look like. Just
command all at the turn
of this is missing this
is going to be based on the floor
of the mine. What did he look like
this driver he was just
a man that he had had interest pulled
out. Writing Arsenal about him.
With
a small Russian and mind you it was only
an impression. That you describe to.
Me which is
a medium of the word where Laughs Well how
sorry you didn't seem to know what about
his coloring was he would you say are blond
I'm afraid I really couldn't tell you
all is good as it gets you
described it to good. Media
in the bank as Officer
I read it see the top.
Well we won't need you on your wife any
longer Mr Prime being. Here here we can be
a number there's just not really cute
enough to help you know the. Good.
Stuff she finally caught up with the. Deal
went over some of these characters did
not drop the date. I've covered everything
I want to bring up today you know I
go to this for
a march today and Fraser Howard for
it. Was found outside the parking lot
as well a New York empty first book from
eleven fifty the Seattle Quimby saw
a car which might have in the guise of
from to write. More to it than that Fraser
park it's car here it's seven now dark
months and said the latest He was shot was
ten that makes
a three hours he was here at the airport I
can't figure out what he was doing here
all the time eating having a meeting
a day. I don't know about dames but I
checked with the bartender and the head
waiter nighttime saw him
tonight you're busy the whole
thing coming here now it looks like
bribery. I can't think why Guy would
shoot less afraid to put
up a fight and he isn't
a big part. Of your oh the night guard
a telephone call for Fraser came in
around nine fifteen over the call
about well the fellow said he was trying
to locate Fraser knew it was going to
Seattle and as to be picked up his ticket
I told him No you asked what flight he
was going on I said the eleven fifty
offered agent but never mind if it
wasn't till then probably you're right
and I was the voice of the herd again.
I might and it in your usual gun four feet
OK thanks you can get some sleep
tonight well looks like you covered
everything so far is going over to face
this place maybe someone there can tell us
some more before my year oh no I was
waiting for you but would do better
we could catch them off balance if there's
anything to learn on their learning are
very fast. I'm still trying to
figure out what I usually don't have near
or for three hours I make on top of what
I mean is your first page here come
visit some up to remember I don't catch
him the best jobs like most
in your check need to run
a mile down and the right arm has been
telling me that for here my street for the
Drum Army.
Around for the summer I'll never get used
to some of them cried some of them find
the ones or just look at
you let's get it over with
I guess breaking the news is
Camera think of Janet and how you.
Want to give it first time you know I
can and reply Yeah thanks you sure it's
OK sure.
Content and raise the bar like this the
uses phrases. To want it and for very well
the roof the roof.
The roof.
There it is out of the band. The
old long you've been home now about half
an hour the one who took care of the
police department the I didn't want the
stuff or the right thing I'm up here get
the rules. Are rules.
Passed start by ducking
things like. Yourself.
The way the world is for you the
we'll see you up there were sure I
would come down she said
her sitting room for
a way. Around
.
The lobby and.
This razor Yes I'm a tenant
color police department is
a detective come by but
if it's anything wrong
it's about Mr Fraser I'm sorry to have
to break it to you as your husband was
killed the night at the airport on
Tuesday and I know he was shocked shocked
I'm sorry to have to
question you like this for
a time I could be of any
help point is that. You know
your husband was going on this trip because
he was flying to Seattle salmon fishing
. The oftentimes you know what finally
was taken by I'm not sure. The
left foot in the building
up is richer as. He wasn't
just
a slight follower of that did he have any any
enemies that you know of course. Everyone
like he was kind. Of picked just can't
believe it I can't believe
that anyone would do
a thing like that is that while it
was found near him with no money and
but he always carries
a lot of money on to Pipetta I don't
want to leave when I mean he could act.
In the morning the.
Winner on the sofa quick
no pillows if I had low speed up.
Your right should we get
a doctor. Told you these things are
tough. Take it easy I'm stylish
Is there anything we can get you
know it's just. Only yes about
politics. And maybe someone want to make
it look that way tell me Mrs Brady has
been mentioned in the front which I want
to say there for you know he didn't say
any about it to me but as it keeps cars
from an exegesis of anything would be in
his room across the hall not if we have
a lot. Of money for you to come. Along
the.
Lines right. Are going to out for.
The. The
women even burning down. For one.
Year with the bills but they should be
this large been broken Oh
but the big thing Jemaine.
Me to them I mean you
know the mood like the
fresh snow job and.
The lock on the French door are over oh
well it happened last week we came home and
I forgot my feet we didn't want to wait
didn't know how time talking and brocade
Aruba very rough for. Our girl in the
morning you're the oldest but we had fun
African on the board of fish yes of course
it than anything else you think of any
reason why Mr Fraser was in the airport
for three hours let us know. You're not
going to get married. All
right don't want the
guy do all that time we did need
to have a frank then I am not
a good thing how do you feel when the time
well I wanted to go thank you will find
. Say I both sorry for the wife
a new. Teacher not the kind you
go for. Her is from our book
feel sorry for the man page the book
supposed the body was moved where suggested
the dark months and then the three
hours to be explained by better and one
thing never take your case to bed. To be
Janet for that one look at
I want to ask if this is my
first time out I'm done.
You. Do any better. To read you.
Both the bill of the thirty eight caliber
and not you are bad say they don't have
a short doubt about this
or the thing to that gun factory ban
you know record up in the top. Five
rush. Around like got us nowhere fast
you know the gun we're
looking for what we want
a life sized think truly killer I want to
find out more about Fraser and Mrs Fraser
I flew around with a gun one minute
of the time if you could run
a check for gun you will get
a quote of that in the paper very funny
why don't you get smart and come to the
pawnshop I thought pawnbrokers response
to report all deals with guns and I will
but take that time we can't
afford to waste it or give
a shit home for this guy was dumb enough
to buy the thing suppose you kept it or
dumped in the bay mail
it to his mother right
where you keep out of trouble of
a Mara I'm going to
deliver the church. Had
planned to probably
seventy. And I haven't had
a chance. To do you
want to now count eight
seven upon them I've minutes where have
you been see Janet I vote tonight was
supposed to be strictly fair but I had to
ask you something we're going to put off
the honeymoon. That won't
be necessary Mona be gone
a week and of the way to get back look
at this is my big chance you know
a good one maybe the. To
Postpone the wedding to nose third.
Word to Mr Collins we've got
fourteen hours. From. Singapore and.
Even if it. Doesn't stop
a day. Then
.
I think the driver's license Oh if you
tell us. I didn't recognize all the top of
the car either it's my wife. If you're going
to get married lucky guy Gratulations
this is common I was talking your brother
about the other night on the bridge all
when was that Saturday night cause.
He was headed for Sausalito with
a big smile on his face
tell me did he have
a girl with him on the phone line Well
he's he's been holding off on me trying to
get me to forget about this think it's
not going to give us what i know i have
still I know you're floating on air
but don't try it for winter thank.
You.
The. Non-tax raped. Me.
Now I know. I'm trying to find out rather
gone to city oh coming up rather go
across the bridge that arose in.
The wrong side of the convenience.
And I wanted to look at you. Tighten
that. Balance and check things of ten
guys. Missing out on crime
in San Francisco going to
make and I don't.
Want to rush it out the ramp what Jill
is on the loose again makes you think
you know the model like
a stalled up less. Guilty on A quick to
slug than it does like phrases they dug one
long out of the wall same gun and I get
the gun now but all three slugs not the
ones that afraid to have
a look. You
can't ask for better odds than
that one on the left kill
a great one on the right on.
Which I agree that this
character for both jobs no matter which
really catch you if you catch these
extra saves you have to figure out the odds
with no two guns with Mark and the same
. You take the count up to it but
a million. The. Leak
or. The or the or. There is
a third reason our sniper had gone that
Martin job was on Osama or
I'm well aware sure and it
is true but I'm centers or went
on to write or read. The post.
Where you are in with dark one some but
phrases body being moved they had all that
liquor store shooting last night well that's
right of them going to go that's funny
was fun doesn't make sense
dream on your own time where
the OP lead good ol A third precinct work
with both right when do I say yo later
after I cleared up go. For.
The or the or.
And what happened you don't need anything
around nothing's wrong coming in. About
that phone I will be to do that again from
now on I get in touch with you when it's
mine you know mass things I'm only going
to get away with but I would be getting
a break so far. The most
your keyboard around
a new read on the gun that the gun was in
the band never for can happen but it has
our two guns in my match I saw the
birds I mean that when you die.
And. You Marry Me. Your copyright. You
want to keep on being
a believer what else are on
I'm out of money and. Watch
a million or two between friends.
And family just happen enough
as it goes down and right is now I just
feel excited tries what makes you think it
would work this time what I had planned is
improving. I'm not sure sometimes. But I
know you're too rare baby you change your
mind to sit still and you have through
your through trying to find my the button
you like somebody on the black night
tonight but you you're
a prey you look so sure
when you found them. Home.
Easy baby watch the temperature at
dusk get away from the South when you.
Say to be stranded in most
cities. You think I'd have
been. Unanimous.
To find out anything at the
airport. Parking lot guys as
a matter of the shots and taking of REVLIMID
is wrong when you backtrack didn't see
anyone else but nothing out
there that you've done are you
sure but absolutely sure absolutely sure
woman from. Mrs cap
a twenty two forty three Ocean Front
Thanks Rush is going to save me
a lot of trouble let's go.
This guy. Looks like I
don't know much about son.
John John John we have to tell of this
man up and down the what you set up with
a certain amount of this done it only
a little bit it's a bit of it left
a lot of random. You see
I got it all right to
go back to my work not today Come on boys
want to take me home your wife brought me
back my mouth.
Like I thought you were buying the boat
it's Rambam when we go out it's there when
we come back the next time to save us about
lemon fighting or something left out of
anybody before but I've been doing that
in English please when I come home I give
the gun to Mom Yes and I put a key
a little on with my dish towel and covered
anyone else know it's there oh no no no
one look you know what
we went on when I put
a coat on and I thought of the smell of
the day for money filled by someone who
will buy you want to see Michael five
nights in you and I'm on anyone else living
we have
a boy in need our printing was plenty nice
to begin with because it did not know
about the gun no need only reason we can
only do gravity works well yes and our job
and. Our job but he's
a good boy or he thank you page need to
be that gentleman you've been through and
you want to get a good
job he's going to make
a lot of money as you do not last night
night before Saturday night he was
here all night on the top line on the right
of the NG I days when he doesn't win
and got others he knew from the delivery
Jeff I'll grant that I think where is he
now Maggie go to school
and thank you for what
I wanted to need to have this meeting
he. Did not know about the Connie. Not
something I think you can do but you were
talking about going to be on the top on
the US going to have
a massage go to the club and ask for want
club where I don't know where it's called
the three thousand people just didn't turn
up on the fly my guess that morning the
guy didn't like the idea though
you know the movie Well I'm not.
Around much I think I'll
a tennis player coming I haven't
seen yet but I don't time as
a member even yourself. Needle cafe please
have happened no I don't think it's
companies today so they spend
a lot of time away and these are like the
plate full of problems you have with that
I don't have some of it so what
does it look Bradleys the back.
Of the the.
Green.
Enough. To.
Make you need every got
a cup Adding out exactly how to get to
like a star can have I was nine and a like
a star I didn't kill any like
a guy has to this story. And keep on
writing me another two I end up in
a thing on me OK me don't take it easy it
was all very friendly we enjoyed talking
you are an interesting guy have secrets I
got my own cigarettes right up until you
tease him that well. Yeah not this is an
element of the fact I am
OK some of the things.
You know you're
a peanut brain you makes driven mistakes
What for instance you searched your room.
And I think playing at my mother keep
it that way nice all polished brass bed
behavior to take it apart. But his
body found stuffed down on the job.
Two rolls of money and I don't
attract the money I know I don't
like you save to buy low shop
corrodes your mother goes around in
a cotton dress my home and if you have ever
leave out of it OK you want to attract
how much was the divine entity about five
hundred was stolen it was yours with me
and I wasn't any anybody
else telling that attract
interesting story about this money don't
the man you killed left a widow I think
a lot of money to be told to take the polls
you're not to bottle up account of what
she was making change were custom out
I know anything about that. Wine
red wine spilled into
a cash register store one of us money
at the track we're going to need oh
it's not mine don't go into Planet we're
trying to trick you if you're smart
want to watch out you don't get your story
twisted and fall on your face. Doing at
the airport setting and when I was at
any airport funny you're going to kill
a man how and I've never been a damper
to tell you split with his he got
a car you know makes sense you haven't got
a car I know I did but your friends have
cars some color the whole keep track of
the color black red green brown take your
pick no green now on every other color
but no green now need all we got you on
the mountain Joy I want to come clean on
this one by the time we at the
airport trying to find that I.
Haven't got a cop timing at
a time well that's flat.
And he killed Martin
and why do you keep trying to pin
the airport job on him. Marna.
I don't think he did it. Came from. His
father didn't find until two hours after
Frazier was dead so he wouldn't you
rather save your kid more gas chamber.
Kept going to have a gun
a month. To the from that out and out of
Mission Park jump the gun on his father's
just going to do that again for the winter
so I chop after the old man to get the
power but he got there for three hours
when your throw out that crystal ball and
think of the fact all right that where the
money the phrase This was why wasn't it
stashed away in the same fight again getting
your first fish you got an offer of.
Whatever for your company for
our fourth victim of. OK.
To relax and be on official business
that's not what fathers and mothers
imagine my. Mandate to be for sure get
a. Job or grow up what is right
and only that. But in my case I
ever not for any reason Rush or agree
on that and. The rain lightning
and other wind Lekovic I think are
no go home for.
The most.
Oh are you really are just drove off by
our thunder Well I want to check on
something this is for ages that are on
there and we were talking about her
husband. When she said you want to have
a fishing because you know South Asians
pro-democracy you walk on the run
why didn't she murmured you been married
a bit longer I want to time off
remember Sam. What are you doing.
Wow Man you're right but I didn't make
a good diet operating this I don't know
maybe I'd better go to that I only got to
your room and then go on
board the only warning will.
Be well I guess I wasted it to.
Be in the morning.
I've got not yet been fast enough that
my lot in the back of the money and
power.
To any of my one balmy
nothing was home alone
and. Figure in the pulling apart
last night you lied to me. And you're just
a mad sorry about your first case about
the make you feel better off you.
Know
a hard on. The
in the
ear the
a. Police
Headquarters with. A lot of defective
Come on give me highway patrol
all up it's Officer player there a boy and
a column listen remember you telling
me about it being on the bridge one
time when I don't know like I said though
you can find on the radio the second all
points broadcast on your application through
I will talk with my back to the Board
place your log column
again and you give me
communications radio play radio
a. Second all points out of the night off.
Of
a call twenty eight the way. An
attempt at the seven pm. Remember
on.
Sunday I got that without
you knowing I have got.
To.
The letter Brant. Got some news for
you Preston found some nice fat
fingerprints on the show Vito's
when he reloaded look at
your right mind of pride fire your car for
a while Want to go to the doctor's room
you didn't have your first five for the
job to do I'm going to have another go to
over the need of us after
about two o'clock to be that.
I want to cooperate but I can't afford it
but I did and I want you to think of me
and I know have never seen this
car before the old that is
the airport it is well you got
one just like this I'm sure what
colors this green blue I
think it's ridiculous
you mean to tell me that I
don't know one color blind.
Down I bought one for not only
didn't it come down to nothing as
for prosecuting I went over the UK
we just borrowed my car and skip
the do that dive in my buddy Rahm
on
a ride CD each of them cry every
couple of B.'s about one dollar
fifty how they are that I'm not going to
live through enough awful morning about
anything good done
a good amount of
give or want our fun and it doesn't show
up in an argument or right yeah yeah
.
At the Grammys beginning. Worked
on gone my brother find you
today yes he did I want to congratulate
you that if that was fast work it seems
I misled you on the color but I'm sure it's
the same car or one like it if you are
on the owner already. The on the
ramp on.
The mat warning or.
The roof. Or.
In the the roof the I.
Mean you're going over
findin out
a few Next time take
care of the planet first
somewhere in
a rush to do it for it to run
kill Fraser your grant for sure was
his Mrs Fraser all along
sure can dream up didn't
dream up you tell me she was half doped and
bad when I'd seen her at the window or
you'll be in on the bridge at eleven and
toss and I got off and I wish it had gone
in the drink myself
you know the same thing and having to
a lot of rookies I'd knock area give me one
brightness of my the mastermind running
around like cocktail fever the rest
of the whole population or blowing
a topic and go on for going
into headquarters and
Quimby identified your car crazy. He's
colorblind. That makes fun of the
eight thousand boobs in the city you
got married to mine I've
been working my way up from
a four since you were in grade school.
Do you think I'd show that away on
a soccer player like Yes For one thing
a dame who said she wasn't
good for you or my brother
read I hate this and other guys after you
first go and see it she got it got
a snap out of it. Her
in her an. Order.
To. This phrase
person can ask a question or
something's not there Ari on
a given ten minutes when our. Very first
want to go I do want to see you again
I think I am sorry I'll tell you one.
Thing. In the war and.
One the funny one like ever.
How much time. Is the time
of CULLEN There. On Ozark no
tax. Pledge. Our.
Thanks.
I'd rather not have.
Operated to keep trying
on pretty sure some of.
The.
Operators got me please according to
please quickly. What I mean that's likely
to be just about make it to
seat damage John Kerry Johns.
Come up. To me take my
car for the take my.
And I get the same as the moment. First get
the radio room on the phone and it's on
the floor. The in
a will get added find out. You know which
is business could we talk to him pleading
with him I could make it would be black
and it can be boring I don't believe that
nobody can always find something in our
mind on the market and it's common to
promise I don't want to know us
right here want it on fire here are
a couple of police letting out of city
and police car lights around three seven
cars are repayed tennis ball
and woman only ever crowd.
Are anywhere that was on skyline of our
town and I don't want to break the.
Ice Age rock one three
seven reporting bus driver
a four star which makes one three
seven or four I weigh one. Hundred
thirty seven Rogers are
one. Point five right in
the middle of
a soda are one level that I take
the wife owns your stay home with
I work here not on the scale
of an eight product right I.
Want to make sure he stays home and
follows he leaves the house I want
a report on the place he goes OK that's
what I get shot to see and he goes No Am I
. Right on the up stairs
Olson said this isn't to
a case I get all. The
money you're going to do
it now if they can't get out
of town for a while. I've got
a hunch I know where it is. A
man managed.
To make an arch enemy but not this time
too many times before but never go far
journey six ways around a
town with a better chance of
a good doctor. Want to be stopped
checked their crime and the
man.
Man the budget. Plan.
Man A. Man and the
friend girlfriend.
Come my general manager. Man
man. And.
I'll take a look at you drive
a. Mandolin. An
.
Architect out of spite.
To get back to try to.
Him.
One point read
a move. Your arms were on Flight.
Day. Three on
guard at the restaurant or
the other. At the back door.
And. You're not walking
around you know get
up there get out and I would not be the
bit like me but it's too obvious going to
drive
a. Car
.
Bomb.
And.
I'm.
Not.
Going to monitor for you half an
hour. Let's get in out of the wind.
And we've got time I'll press on. And.
Our. Why. You said at one
time of the year I'm
not. To get past the subway anyway knock
on honeycomb I can see that we're
gonna cost.
Miming in the movie with
them in one minute when I'm
in.
The war in.
The name. Of the
man or.
The al.